Guide to the Stewart M. Brandborg Papers 1932-2000
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- The Wilderness Society, 1930-1977; Series IV; 28.0 linear ft.
  - Subject Files, 1930-1977; Subseries 2; 25.75 linear ft.
    - Livestock on Public Lands, 1968 (Box-folder 41/11)
    - Living Wilderness, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 41/12)
    - Living Wilderness Article, 1975 (Box-folder 41/13)
    - Living Wilderness Plans, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41/14)
    - Logging Information and Articles, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 41/15)
    - Benton MacKaye Memorial, 1975 (Box-folder 41/16)
    - Magruder Corridor, Upper Selway, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 42/1-2)
    - Mailers, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Management Exercise, Ohio State Automobile Association, 1967 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Management of Bears in Yellowstone National Park, 1967 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - Maps, 1964 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - March Washington Seminar, 1972 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - Marine Sanctuary Study Bill, 1968 (Box-folder 42/8)
    - George Marshall, Complaints, 1974 (Box-folder 42/9)
    - George Marshall, Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 42/10)
    - George Marshall, Program Criticism, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 42/11)
    - John Marshall for Senate, 1974 (Box-folder 42/12)
    - Maryland Conservation Council, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 42/13)
    - Maryland House of Delegates, Bills on Wilderness, 1969 (Box-folder 42/14)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 42/15)
    - Massachusetts Audubon Society, 1975 (Box-folder 42/16)
    - Materials for Use in Preparation of Protest, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 42/17)
    - Materials for Use in Preparation of Protest, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 43/1-2)
    - Jean Matthews, Wilderness Speeches, 1974 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - Eugene McCarthy, Clippings and Notes, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - George McGovern, 1972 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - John R. McGuire, Forest Service Chief, 1954-1974 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - Media Campaign-Newspaper Plan, 1973 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - Member Mailings, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - Membership and Member Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - Membership Funding, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Membership Information and Correspondence, Howard Zahniser, 1964 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - Membership Mailings, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - Membership Mailings, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - Clif Merritt, Articles, 1970 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - Clifton Merritt, Correspondence and Statements, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - Messinger Wilderness Seminar, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 43/16)
    - Michigan Wilderness and Isle Royale, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 44/10)
    - Minerals Policy and Mining Laws, 1953-1969 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - Minerals vs. Wilderness, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 44/12)
    - Mining Law, 1969 (Box-folder 44/13)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 44/19-20)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 44/21)
    - Missouri River, Montana, 1967 (Box-folder 44/14)
    - Model State Workshop, 1975 (Box-folder 44/15)
    - Montana League of Conservation Voters, 1975 (Box-folder 44/17)
    - Montana Outdoors, 1975 (Box-folder 44/18)
    - Montana Wilderness and Wildlife Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 44/22-23)
    - Montana Wilderness Association, 1960-1977 (Box-folder 45/1-2)
    - Montana Wilderness Bill, 1975 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Montana Wildlife Federation, Proposal for Improving Wildlife and Land Resource Management, undated (Box-folder 45/4)
    - Motor Vehicles on Public Lands, 1964 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - Mount Jefferson Wilderness Area, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 45/6)
    - Mount Jefferson Wilderness Area Proposal, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 45/7-8)
    - Mountain Goat Article, 1968 (Box-folder 45/9)
    - Mountain Goats, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 45/10)
    - Multiple Use Plan Skalkaho-Bird and Sleeping Child Planning Units, 1973 (Box-folder 45/11)
    - Multiple Use Plan-Burnt Fork Planning Unit, 1972 (Box-folder 45/12)
    - Margaret Murie Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 45/13)
    - Murie-Broome Awards, 1969 (Box-folder 45/14)
    - National Commission on Water Quality, 1975 (Box-folder 45/15)
    - National Conference on Environmental Leadership, 1975 (Box-folder 45/16)
    - National Forest Timber Conservation and Management Act, 1969 (Box-folder 45/17)
    - National Forest Wilderness and National Forest Primitive Areas, undated (Box-folder 46/1)
    - National Interest Amendments, 1971 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - National Park Service, 1967 (Box-folder 46/3)
    - National Park Service, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 46/4-5)
    - National Park Service Brochures, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 46/6)
    - National Park Service Bureau of Sport Fisheries and Wildlife Wilderness Hearing Announcements, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 46/7)
    - National Park Service Clippings, 1972 (Box-folder 46/8)
    - National Park Service Coop Program, 1975 (Box-folder 46/9)
    - National Park Service Leadership and Conservation Cooperative, 1974 (Box-folder 46/10)
    - National Parks for the Future, Press Coverage and Editorial Reaction, 1972 (Box-folder 46/11)
    - National Public Lands Task Force, Charles Watson, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 46/12)
    - National Resources Council of America, 1973 (Box-folder 46/13)
    - National Resources Council of America, 1975 (Box-folder 46/14)
    - Natural Resources Council of America, Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 46/15)
    - National Timber Bills Correspondence, 1954-1970 (Box-folder 46/16)
    - National Timber Supply Act, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 46/17-18)
    - National Watershed Congress, 1973 (Box-folder 46/19)
    - National Wild Rivers System, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 47/1-3)
    - National Wilderness Preservation System, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 47/4)
    - National Wildlife Federation Conservation Directory, 1974 (Box-folder 47/5)
    - National Wildlife Refuge System, 1968 (Box-folder 47/6)
    - Native Species Conservation and Enhancement Act, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 47/7)
    - Natural Resources Council of America, 1969 (Box-folder 47/8)
    - Natural Resources Council of America, Legislative News Service, 1968 (Box-folder 47/9)
    - Nature News Notes, Utah Nature Study Society, 1975 (Box-folder 47/10)
    - Nevada Outdoor Recreation Association, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 47/11)
    - Newsletter and Bulletin, 1972 (Box-folder 47/12)
    - Richard Nixon, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 47/13)
    - North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 47/14)
    - North Cascades National Park, 1961-1971 (Box-folder 47/15-16)
    - North Cascades National Park, Mailer Responses, 1970 (Box-folder 47/17)
    - North Cascades Park, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 48/1-2)
    - Northern Environmental Council Grant, 1975 (Box-folder 48/3)
    - Northern Great Plains Action Group, 1975 (Box-folder 48/4)
    - Northern Rockies Action Group, 1975 (Box-folder 48/5)
    - Northern Rockies Action Group, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 48/6)
    - Northwest Conservation Representative, 1972 (Box-folder 48/7)
    - Northwest Wilderness Conference, 1970 (Box-folder 48/8)
    - Northwest Wilderness Conference, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 48/9)
    - Northwest Wilderness Conference, 1974 (Box-folder 48/10)
    - Notes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 48/11)
    - Notes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 48/12)
    - Notes, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 48/13)
    - Notes and Memos on Seminars, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 48/14-15)
    - Notes of Virginia Carney, Meeting of the Wilderness Society Governing Council, 1975 (Box-folder 49/1)
    - Notes to Take Home, Stewart M. Brandborg, 1973 (Box-folder 49/2)
    - O'Hara for Majority Leader, 1970 (Box-folder 49/3)
    - Ohio Conservation Foundation, 1970 (Box-folder 49/4)
    - Oil Industry, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 49/5)
    - Oil-Energy, 1974 (Box-folder 49/6)
    - Richard C. Olson, Reading Copies, 1974 (Box-folder 49/7)
    - Sigurd Olson, Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 49/8)
    - Sigurd Olson, Plans, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 49/9)
    - Operation Grass Roots Concept, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 49/10)
    - Operation Grassroots, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 49/11)
    - Oregon, House Environmental/ Energy Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 49/12)
    - Organic School Workshops, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 49/13)
    - Organizational Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 49/14)
    - Outdoor Recreation Use and the Public Lands, Public Land Law Review Commission, 1969 (Box-folder 49/15)
    - Outer Continental Shelf Act Notes, undated (Box-folder 49/16)
    - Park Planning Handbook, 1966 (Box-folder 49/17)
    - Pending Issues, 1974 (Box-folder 49/18)
    - Marlin Perkins's, Wild Kingdom Proposal, 1975 (Box-folder 49/19)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 50/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 50/2)
    - Pittsburgh Teach-in, 1970 (Box-folder 50/3)
    - Plans for Trip Program, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 50/4)
    - Point Reyes National Seashore, 1969 (Box-folder 50/5)
    - Possible Management Alternatives for the Idaho and Salmon River Breaks Primitive Area, 1973 (Box-folder 50/6)
    - Possible Management Alternatives for the Salmon River and Adjacent Lands, 1973 (Box-folder 50/7)
    - Press Use Project, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 50/8)
    - Production Forms with List Count, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 50/9)
    - Professional Foresters, 1974 (Box-folder 50/10)
    - Program Development Projects, 1972 (Box-folder 50/11)
    - Project Monitor, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 50/12)
    - Proposed Litigation, 1975 (Box-folder 50/13)
    - Protest in Response to the Internal Revenue Service, 1972 (Box-folder 50/14)
    - Public Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 50/15)
    - Public Domain and Secretary of the Interior Hickel, 1970 (Box-folder 51/1)
    - Public Education Division, 1975 (Box-folder 51/2)
    - Public Equity Corporation, undated (Box-folder 51/3)
    - Public Hearing Statements, Stewart M. Brandborg, 1968 (Box-folder 51/4)
    - Public Involvement, United States Forest Service Roadless Area Review, 1974 (Box-folder 51/5)
    - Publications Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 51/6)
    - Publications Department Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 51/7)
    - Publications Office, 1969 (Box-folder 51/17)
    - Publications, Montana Forest and Conservation Experiment Station, School of Forestry, University of Montana, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 51/4)
    - Put on Newsprint, undated (Box-folder 51/5)
    - Quarterly Report of the Montana Cooperative Wildlife Research Unit, 1965 (Box-folder 51/6)
    - Radio-Television Publicity, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 51/7)
    - Recreational Vehicles (RVs) in National Parks, 1972 (Box-folder 51/8)
    - Redwood Creek, Humboldt County, California, National Park Proposal Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 51/10)
    - Redwood National Park, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 51/9-10)
    - Nathanial Reed, 1973 (Box-folder 51/11)
    - Regulating Regulatory Agencies, undated (Box-folder 51/12)
    - Vic Reinemer, 1964-1976 (Box-folder 51/13)
    - Remarks Given at the Thirteenth Biennial Wilderness Conference, 1973 (Box-folder 51/14)
    - Reorganization of the United States Department of Agriculture and United States Department of the Interior, Dan Poole, undated (Box-folder 51/15)
    - Reports to the Federal Power Commission, 1969 (Box-folder 51/16)
    - Reports: Wildlife and Resource Management, 1930-1968 (Box-folder 52/1)
    - Requests for Photos, undated (Box-folder 52/2)
    - Requests from Members, 1964 (Box-folder 52/3)
    - Return of Lands to the Yakima Indian Reservation, 1972 (Box-folder 52/4)
    - Carolyn Rinehart,Writer and Reporter, 1975 (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Roadless Areas, 1973 (Box-folder 52/6)
    - Roadless Inventories, Forest Service, 1975 (Box-folder 52/7)
    - Roadless National Forest Management, 1975 (Box-folder 52/8)
    - Salmon River Breaks Wilderness Plans, 1973 (Box-folder 52/9)
    - Salmon River Wilderness and Idaho Wilderness, Proposal, 1973 (Box-folder 52/10)
    - Sample Mailings, Other Organizations, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 52/11)
    - Sample Programs, Regional Workshops, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 52/12)
    - San Rafael Wilderness, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 52/13)
    - San Rafael Wilderness Area, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 52/14-15)
    - San Rafael Wilderness Bill, 1967 (Box-folder 52/16)
    - San Rafael Wilderness Bill File, Stewart M. Brandborg, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 53/1-3)
    - San Rafael Wilderness Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 53/4-5)
    - Earl D. Sandvig, 1970 (Box-folder 53/6)
    - Save the Tallgrass Prairie, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 53/7)
    - John Saylor, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Peter Scholes Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 53/9)
    - Doug Scott, 1970 (Box-folder 53/10)
    - Doug Scott Thesis: The Wilderness Act, 1969 (Box-folder 53/11)
    - Douglas W. Scott, Manuscript Draft, Origins and Development of the Wilderness Bill: 1930-1956, undated (Box-folder 53/12-14)
    - Douglas Willard Scott Theses Proposal: The Wilderness Act: A Case Study in Resource Policy Evolution, undated (Box-folder 54/1)
    - Seashore Proposals, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - Second Alaska Purchase, 1972 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Secretary of the Interior Kleppe, 1975 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Secretary of the Interior Morton, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 54/5)
    - Secretary of the Interior Morton, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 54/6-7)
    - Secretary Udall and Secretary Freeman Materials, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 54/8)
    - Self-Support Financing, 1975 (Box-folder 54/9)
    - Selway-Bitterroot Management Plan, 1974 (Box-folder 54/10)
    - Selway-Bitterroot Wilderness, 1964 (Box-folder 54/11)
    - Selway-Bitterroot Wilderness Correspondence, 1956-1968 (Box-folder 54/12)
    - Selway-Bitterroot Wilderness, Frank Church and Lee Metcalf Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 54/13)
    - Selway-Bitterroot Wilderness Management Plan (Review Draft), 1975 (Box-folder 54/14)
    - Selway-Bitterroot Wilderness Notes, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 54/15)
    - Seminar Participants, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 54/16)
    - Seminar Participants and Feedback, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 54/17)
    - Seminar, General Notes and Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Seminars, Workshops, and Training, 1972 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, 1975 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Senate Subcommittee Testimony, 1976 (Box-folder 55/4-5)
    - Senate Wilderness Bills, 1969 (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Senator Hart, Michigan, 1972 (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Senator Henry Jackson, Washington, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 55/8)
    - Senator J. Fulbright, 1973 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Senator John Melcher, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 55/10-12)
    - Senator John Melcher, Montana, 1974 (Box-folder 55/13)
    - Sentman Publishing, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 55/14)
    - September Environment Issues, 1975 (Box-folder 55/15)
    - Sierra Club, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 55/16)
    - Sierra Club Legislation and the IRS, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 55/17)
    - Sierra Club Memos, Washington and Idaho, 1968 (Box-folder 55/18)
    - Sierra Club National News Report, 1975 (Box-folder 55/19)
    - Sierra Club Wilderness Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Silvicultural Systems, Forest Service, 1973 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Dwight R. Smith, Colorado State University, Land Use Seminar Wilderness Paper, 1955-1967 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Society of American Foresters, 1975 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Society of American Foresters, Speech File, 1974 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Speaking Engagements, Sweet Briar College, Virginia, 1972 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Speech Files, American Association of Conservation Information, 1969 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Speech Files, Stewart M. Brandborg, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Speech Files, Fund Raising Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - Speech Files, Georgia Conservation, 1970 (Box-folder 56/11)
    - Speech Files, Reference Materials, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 56/12-13)
    - Speech Files, Research, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 56/14-15)
    - Speech Files, Reuss Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Speech Outlines, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Speech, Northwest Wilderness Conference, Stewart M. Brandborg, 1974 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Speech, Women's National Democratic Club, 1974 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Speeches, Background, and Information, 1958-1975 (Box-folder 57/5-7)
    - Speeches, Stewart M. Brandborg, 1966 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Speeches, General Outline and Format, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Speeches, Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 57/10-11)
    - Speeches, Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box-folder 58/8-9)
    - Speeches, The Wilderness Society, 1958-1974 (Box-folder 58/1-2)
    - St. John River and Dickey Dam, Maine, 1969 (Box-folder 58/3)
    - St. Louis Regional Conference, 1974 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - George H. Stankey, Publications, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - State and Regional Environmental Leaders Workshop, 1972 (Box-folder 58/6)
    - State Committees on Wilderness, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 58/7)
    - State Workshops, Alabama-Missouri, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 59/1-2)
    - State Workshops, Montana-Wyoming, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 59/3-5)
    - Statement of George Alderson, Director of Federal Affairs, 1974 (Box-folder 59/6)
    - Statement of Support of Proposed Redwood National Park, 1965 (Box-folder 59/7)
    - Statements and Testimony, Subcommittee on Public Lands, Interior and Insular Affairs Committee, House of Representatives, 1973 (Box-folder 59/8)
    - Stratified Primitive Area, 1966 (Box-folder 59/9)
    - Strip Mining, 1974 (Box-folder 59/10)
    - Student Conservation Program, 1975 (Box-folder 59/11)
    - Students, Interviews, Surveys, etc., 1975 (Box-folder 59/12)
    - Summary of Economic Information Related to the Two Pipeline Alternatives, undated (Box-folder 59/13-14)
    - Summary Proposal for the Salmon River-Idaho, 1973 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - Summit Conference on Energy, Sugarloaf, 1974 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Sun Butte Dam, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Supersonic Transport (SST) Senate Vote, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - Symposium and Meeting Proceedings, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - Symposiums and Dedications, 1975 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Taos Pueblo, H.R. 3306, 1969 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Tax Law Change, Internal Revenue Service, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Tax Study, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Tax Study Appendix (K-1), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Tax Study, Internal Revenue Service, 1970 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - Tax Study, Internal Revenue Service, 1972 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Tax Study Notes, Internal Revenue Service, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - Testimony, Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, 1968 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Teton Sciences Summer School End of summer Report, 1968 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Texas Marine Sanctuary, 1969 (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Think Tank Project, 1973 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - Three Sisters Wilderness Area, 1972 (Box-folder 61/7)
    - Timber, 1971 (Box-folder 61/8-9)
    - Timber, 1973 (Box-folder 61/10)
    - Timber Fight, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 61/11)
    - Timber Harvest on Public Lands, Articles, Notes, Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 61/12)
    - Timber Harvest on Public Lands, Committees, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - Timber Industry Advertisements and Responses, 1975 (Box-folder 61/14)
    - Timber, Mailings to Timber Corporations, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 62/1-2)
    - Training Course for Conservation Activists, 1968 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Training for Communicating with Congress, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Thurman Trosper Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - Unanswered Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - Trout Unlimited, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Trout Unlimited, 1973 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Trustees for Conservation, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Trustees for Conservation, 1975 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Morris Udall, 1974 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Morris Udall, Presidential Campaign, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - Stewart Udall, 1971 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - United Nations Environment Programme, 1975 (Box-folder 62/14)
    - Unity Group Notes, 1975 (Box-folder 62/15)
    - Unity Groups and Contacts, undated (Box-folder 62/16-17)
    - University of Idaho Advisory Council, College of Forestry, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - University of Montana Bitterroot Study, 1974 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - University Publications on Natural Resources, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Upper Missouri River Plans, 1975 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - Upper Selway-Magruder Corridor, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 63/5-6)
    - Urban Environment Conference, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - Valley of the Giants, 1975 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - Ventana and Desolation Valley Wilderness Bills, 1969 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - Ventana Wilderness Area, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - Voyageurs, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Voyageurs National Park, 1970 (Box-folder 63/12)
    - Voyageurs National Park Association, 1975 (Box-folder 63/13)
    - Ronald Walker, 1973 (Box-folder 63/14)
    - Director of the National Park Service Ronald Walker, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 63/15)
    - Wambach Report, S. 393, 1975 (Box-folder 63/16)
    - Washakie Wilderness Proposal, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - Washington Seminar, 1971 (Box-folder 64/2-3)
    - May Washington Seminar, 1972 (Box-folder 64/4)
    - Washington Seminar, 1973 (Box-folder 64/5-6)
    - Washington Seminar, 1975 (Box-folder 64/7)
    - Washington Wilderness Seminar, 1973 (Box-folder 64/8-10)
    - Washington Wilderness System, undated (Box-folder 64/11)
    - Waterless Waste Disposal, Howard H. Leich, 1974 (Box-folder 64/12)
    - West Virginia Highlands Conservancy vs. Island Creek Coal Company, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 64/13)
    - Western Trip, People to See, 1972 (Box-folder 64/14)
    - White House, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 64/15)
    - White House Bureau of the Budget, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 65/1-2)
    - Wild and Scenic Rivers, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - Wild Missouri River, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - Wild Rivers, Craighead Brothers, Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 65/5)
    - Wilderness Act Analysis, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - Wilderness Act Handbook, Initial Effort to Write Citizen Guide for Wilderness Review, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - Wilderness Act Regulations, Mines and Mining, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - Wilderness Act, 10th Anniversary Observance, 1972 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - Wilderness Area Files, Brandborg, Stewart, Lincoln-Scapegoat, Montana and San Gabriel, California, 1943-1976 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - Wilderness Area Reviews, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Wilderness Areas, Congressional Reports and Records, 1964 (Box-folder 65/12)
    - Wilderness Awareness Teacher Training, 1969 (Box-folder 65/13)
    - Wilderness Bill, National Organizations, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 65/14)
    - Wilderness Bills, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 66/1-2)
    - Wilderness Bills, 1965-1972 (Box-folder 66/3-4)
    - Wilderness Bills, Sycamore Canyon, Pine Mountain, Mount Baldy, Wisconsin Islands, Correspondence and Testimony, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Wilderness Committee, Maryland, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Wilderness Committee, Virginia, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Wilderness Committee, Washington D.C., 1966-1970 (Box-folder 66/8-10)
    - Wilderness Conservation Leader's Background Information Kit, 1956-1967 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - Wilderness Conservation Leader's Background Information Kit, 1956-1967 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Wilderness Conservation Leader's Background Information Kit, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 67/2-3)
    - Wilderness Decision Making, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Wilderness Education, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Wilderness Foundation, 1975 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Wilderness Handbook Outline, undated (Box-folder 67/7)